<Document>
  # Blueshield Officer

  The [color=#258]Blueshield Officer[/color] is an elite bodyguard unit sent by [color=#282]Central Command[/color], tasked with protecting the [color=yellow]Heads of Staff[/color] and designated [color=yellow]VIPs[/color] aboard the station.
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ToyFigurineChaplain" Caption="I HAVE A GUN!"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ToyFigurineBlueshield" Caption="MR. QM GET DOWN!"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ToyFigurineQuartermaster" Caption="AHHHH!"/>
  </Box>

  As the station's BSO you are part of the [color=yellow]Command[/color] department; and are, foremost, tasked with protecting fellow members of Command. You are however, sent by [color=#282]CentComm[/color], and are part of Central Command. Meaning you can technically refuse orders from the [color=yellow]Captain[/color], if they go against the interests of NanoTrasen.

  You are given a [color=#258]Central Command encryption key[/color] in your headset, which functions as a direct, long range link between you and CentComm, allowing you to speak to commanders across space. [bold]There isn't always someone manning the line[/bold] though, so you might need to get Central's attention with a stamped fax, unless they make contact first.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHeadsetBlueshield" Caption="headset"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="EncryptionKeyCentCom" Caption="encryption key"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RubberStampBlueshield" Caption="stamp"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="FaxMachineBase" Caption="fax machine"/>
  </Box>

  You are a member of [color=red]Security[/color] [bold]only by technicality[/bold] To permit the use of security contraband in your line of work! You do not perform the job of a security officer. You do not go after people with a wanted status, you don't even get to see that! After all, if you're arresting the clown, you're not protecting a head of staff! You are able to enter Security locked areas only when the station is on [bold]extended access.[/bold] That is, when the station is critically understaffed.


  ## Your Toys

  As a Blueshield Officer you are issued 
</Document>
